It's Friday!
The best day of the week.
It's happening.
It's truly happening.
Guys, I have been fucking suffering since the last dream, because this run is insane that I'm in right now, and I can't wait to continue, although I am ready to just instantly die to some bullshit.
So, I'm preparing myself mentally for that.
I don't have any high expectations for anything.
But, I am excited.
Happy Friday.
Half-loaf!
Thank you for giving out 10 community subs!
14 minutes ago, thank you so much, if you're still here.
I really, really appreciate that.
I'm just so happy that you enjoyed so much.
That you did that.
Half-loaf.
Hey, there you are.
Thank you, man.
I hope you're having a wonderful Friday.
Are you doing good?
Are you prepared to watch me win?
You're on a road trip?
Huh.
Thank you for the wonderful watching experience.
Thank you for supporting me.
I really appreciate it.
I'm glad VODs on Twitch are enabled, so I can catch up if I leave to do something else.
Yeah, so I disabled that last week, because I thought it would be confusing to have both VODs on Twitch and YouTube.
But people really like the VODs on Twitch, so I just put them back on.
So there you go.
Oh, wait, is it High's birthday today?
Happy birthday, man.
Road trip and birthday.
That's cool.
I gotta be right back real quick.
I had to open the window, because it's actually hot as hell in here.
Oh, yeah.
Modding from the car?
Damn.
I love it.
I love how everyone has done this.
I love this community.
You guys are awesome.
Okay, let me...
Man, I actually, for some reason, I always store my keyboard away in my drawer every time I finish playing Noita.
Let me connect it.
There we go.
Okay, guys, I'm way too excited.
I gotta get right into it.
And I've been thinking about this run, by the way.
I've been thinking, and I have ideas.
I have ideas.
Let's see here.
Also, I'm gonna turn off the singing bowls, of course.
Can't have the singing bowls while we play.
Okay, I'm jumping in.
So basically, here's my thoughts.
I'm gonna spend some time just, you know, acquainting myself with what the fuck I did last time.
Wait, I have perks I didn't take?
I don't remember this.
Wait a minute.
Right, I made it to a new zone.
I remember this now.
I made it to a new zone.
I did not pick up the hearts.
Oh, and I have a bunch of stuff I can do.
I have a bunch of stuff I can do.
So basically what I was thinking is, I know I can get back to the top if I really want it.
And now that I'm a powerful mage, I thought it would be really cool to go explore the top.
This is my shot, you know?
I'm finally powerful.
I always get my ass kicked up there, so this is the moment.
This wand is some bullshit, by the way.
We gotta fix that one.
That's just not good at all, is it?
It's terrible.
And I have all these things here as well.
This one, Bloodlust.
A projectile gains a hefty damage boost, but is also able to hurt you.
See, that's a bit of a silver-edged, you know?
Silver-edged, no, double-edged sword.
Bling too much Dota, I guess.
It sounds really good.
33 damage on each of these when it shoots this fast?
I mean, it's already doing sick amounts of damage, right?
Do I really need the extra is what I'm thinking?
Probably not.
I need an actual wand that is not a shuffle, so I can predictably throw these things.
So the question, to get back up... Oh yeah, wait, wait, wait, I discovered this.
Watch this, watch this.
You see this hole right here?
This allows me to exit and come back and edit my wands later.
That's what I figured out.
That was one of the last things I figured out.
This down here is the new region I haven't been in yet.
And look at the walls.
There's black holes on the walls.
So maybe the people in this region are cosmic in nature or they, I don't know, praise the celestial bodies or something, you know?
Also, I can levitate quite high using... No!
Well, you know what?
At least I confirmed things.
I have no words for what I just did.
I'm gonna take a sip here.
Don't matter.
It's fine.
Everything's fine.
That was a bit of a bummer there.
I can't believe I just did that.
But, you know what?
Now it is 100% confirmed.
There's a spot right here.
Or like here.
Somewhere here.
If you pass this, everything collapses.
Oh god.
Well, that wasn't that great, was it?
That was terrible.
Let me... Boink!
Clean that up.
Man, the sound effect of that bomb is like haunting.
It's not just an explosion.
It's almost like a whooshing sound.
Like a million ghosts dying, you know?
Something like that at least.
Let's do it again.
Just one more.
I just want to clean it.
Hide!
Okay.
I can still do this though.
Oh, can I get up here?
Yeah, okay.
So what do I want?
Extra want capacity.
I don't think I want this.
I thought this was like an extra want slot up here, but that's not what it is.
Enemy radar?
I feel like that's kind of useless.
I don't know how it works though.
But I definitely want to save up some money to buy that one.
Maybe you should just explore it a little bit here.
Gather just a bit of money.
You know?
Just get $1600 and then we'll see what happens.
That's an enemy.
It's an evil crystal of some sort.
Oh, it's doing things.
Hello?
Wait, what?
Wait a minute.
Collapsed?
I just realized all of this looks like the same material as the holy mountain.
Is this the holy temple?
Where the hell am I?
Oh, this wand dude!
It's so good!
And these enemies have HP.
Like, they are not fucking around.
I'm already at the money!
Incredible.
Well, that was fast.
I guess I'll go back up.
Why was there just a ding sound?
Alright, let's do it.
What do we got?
More love?
We just become more friendly?
Healthy exploration.
Every time you visit a new area, you get... No, I don't like this.
60 health is nothing compared to what I have now.
Extra health, one off.
You gain 50% extra maximum health?
Ooh, with the amount I have now?
That would be sick.
That would be really sick.
I'm doing it, I'm doing it.
Ooh, that's sick!
Oh, yeah!
Oh, man.
Okay.
Awesome.
So, let's see if I can't get back up.
How would I do this?
Just dig a hole, right?
Do I have anything that can dig?
I mean, I have the black holes actually.
Oh, but I can't edit the thing anymore, so...
But I can sort of gamble on getting a black hole.
Oh, but why is it moving so slow?
I actually don't understand that.
Speed is 40.
Right?
Why is it so slow?
I think the other time I had a black hole, it was like... It went super quick.
I don't understand that.
Let's do it.
Shit!
Yeah, rip.
Maybe there's a way from the other side here.
Let's take a look.
Wait, do I have a digging... Does this dig at all?
No.
Not really.
Don't take the heart!
That's something I would do.
For sure.
Hmm.
See, now I don't... I'm not so sure.
Maybe I am sort of... Maybe I need to continue exploring here for a bit.
What is this?
Someone friendly fly.
Oh, I haven't even looked at these.
What is that?
Circle of water.
Plasma beam bounce.
Okay.
And the prices are ludicrous right now.
I have 94 bucks to my name.
That is nothing.
Okay.
I'm just gonna explore here.
Maybe we'll find a wand that can dig.
And if I find a wand that can dig, it's go time.
That's the plan.
So that explodes in green acid, I think, or something.
What is this?
Cursed rock!
Whoa, that thing is weird.
Scares me.
Got it.
So don't stand on the cursed rock I imagine.
We could try it though.
Yeah.
It's confirmed.
Whoa!
Okay, okay.
Man, this is bad.
Wait, where are you?
Is he invisible?
Oh no, wait, it's like a trap.
Also, I don't have a lot of water on me.
I have water and steam potion.
It's right there.
I got it.
Why am I taking damage?
Whoa, what the fuck is this?
Man, the recoil is actually gonna fuck me here because if I get recoiled into a wall, I will take damage, you know?
Yo, what was that?
There was the... Oh, I just lost health.
There was the symbol when the thing collapsed.
The fuck is going on here?
This is... Oh, oh shit, what the fuck?
Watch... Oh, it's that thing!
Die, motherfucker!
Dude, this place is not a good place to be.
I don't like the cursed rock.
I don't like that at all.
Kill that thing.
I gotta play this patiently.
What's this?
Diamond?
Cursed rock.
Oh man, I can't stand on any of this shit.
Yeah, I'm gonna be leaking health here slowly for sure.
Oh man, that guy has HP.
Also did a lot of damage to me.
I lost a lot already.
I cannot be stained because I have a... thing.
What is this?
Stainless armor.
If I have no active stain, I take 50% less damage, which is significant.
Hey, can I get rid of the cursed rock?
Let's say I do this.
I... I'm not sure, actually.
Got him.
At least I'm getting a lot of money here.
Kill that guy.
I'm afraid of these wizard looking people because if they have wands, it's super unexpected what may happen.
You know, they could be shooting god knows what.
Crystal.
Kind of wanna...
Nah, I'm just gonna shoot it.
Yep.
Oh!
Okay, it explodes into that sort of weapon that I had earlier, the purple explosion that I used to dig with, if you remember.
Boink.
Nice.
Seems I'm gonna be stuck with... Oh!
Oh my god, HP god!
What the fuck is that?
My spells were looping!
You saw that?
Looked hella cool.
Also scares me, though.
Fuck you!
Oh my god.
They are starting to get tanky.
I don't even know where I'm going.
I mean, I'm getting money quick.
Almost 1800 dollars already.
And I just started.
I had 94 bucks to my... Oh!
94 bucks to my name.
And now I'm already getting up there.
So maybe those prizes in the shop are not as ridiculous.
What the fuck?
Why is that rock so weirdly shaped?
Aha!
It contains explosives.
I am not fooled.
Not at all.
Careful with this acid.
Come on, I saw you up there.
Eee!
Got him.
Let's grab that gold.
I actually need gold.
Whoa, what the fuck is that?
Yo, that just did a sick to...
Holy shit!
That is the craziest enemy.
It took like 300 HP from me.
God damn.
What is that?
Okay.
Whoa!
God damn it, I missed it.
Kill that guy.
Give me money.
I can't get to the gold.
That works.
There's something over there.
In here.
Something that scares me.
What is going on with this bone dust?
It's like one of those fucked up chemical reactions you see on YouTube.
I see you there.
Come on.
Explode into a massive chaotic explosion.
I know you wanna.
There it goes.
Oh!
That just cursed the rock.
Aha!
So that's what's happening.
What if I cover the cursed rock with this substance down there?
Can I uncurse the rock?
Actually, I think I can.
Purifying powder or some... or purifying water.
I had that once, remember?
Take my way in there.
Also, I do have invisiblium and acceleratium.
I have to remember this.
If I need to be invisible, it can happen.
And I can't drink it.
I need to pour it on myself.
Tea.
Right, I have to remember my key bindings.
Here we go.
Ooh, what the hell?
There's lava in there.
Fuck yeah.
Whoa, that didn't even dig through the wall.
Okay, I guess I need the black hole.
Boink!
Wait.
Shit, wrong one.
There we go.
Why are things exploding over there?
This lava scares me.
Okay.
Magic missile.
2200 mana on this.
Do I want this at all?
Maybe.
That doesn't dig through this, right?
It does not.
So I will not be taking it.
Yo, there's some perpetually fireworks thing going on here.
It scares me.
Okay.
Look at the background with the pillars and stuff.
This is definitely a huge ass tent.
Maybe this is the holy mountain of all the holy mountains.
The symbol appeared again.
It's the same symbol when the holy mountain collapses.
I wonder what this means.
Let's get rid of this guy up here.
Why?
That's scary.
Whew.
Okay.
Hey, okay, crystal.
We can kill that.
Got it.
Cool.
That's such a cool effect.
Oh, actually, that is making this really dense rock collapse, right?
So it's like a very powerful force when those things explode.
What is that?
Some kind of brazier, I think.
I hear a gong.
Is it mealtime?
What the hell is that?
I don't like that.
That scares me.
Fuck you.
Wait, they're killing each other.
Awesome.
Thank you.
Oh!
It's a trap.
We're fine.
Kill it.
I have to remember, I can still heal in the holy mountain.
This music is creeping me out.
Love the particle effects.
It's some of the best ever.
There's stuff up here, too.
Oh, man.
I really need a proper... I need...
I need a plasma thingy.
A plasma cutter.
That's what I need.
Remember how I said I would never get rid of one?
I regret that I got rid of one.
That's right.
Thank you.
Scary enemies.
Oh!
I don't like those sounds.
Oh, wait.
Wait a minute.
Can I?
No, this crystal right here is actually...
So this is a green crystal.
This is a purple crystal.
I wonder if I can do something with them.
I'm afraid of kicking it in case it explodes right on me.
But I mean, I am explosion immune.
But, hold on.
Let me see what... Let me confirm here.
What comes out of the green?
Acid?
No, wait.
Oh!
Okay, so the green one makes cursed rock.
Gotcha.
All right.
What does the purple one do?
I think they just explode in the purple mess that causes subsequent explosions.
My poison?
I am.
Wait, what's happening?
Oh, I was standing on cursed rock.
Okay, shit.
I'm an idiot.
Didn't even pay attention.
I'm losing a lot of HP here.
But you know what?
Having all this HP is a great learning experience for me for what to expect in this region, you know?
Whoa.
Hello.
Hide!
Fuck these things.
That's right.
Do not stand on the cursed rock.
It's very bad.
Okay.
There's something up there.
Let's check it out.
I like this region, though.
It's very cool.
Oh!
Invisibilium potion.
Another one.
You know what?
I'm going to start using it.
There's no reason not to.
Invisible me.
There we go.
Okay.
So that one contains water?
What just happened there?
I think.
Let me get in there.
There I look.
Got him.
Dude, it's a Hamus bucket!
What the hell?
Is this how Hamuses are made?
Uh...
What do we have there?
Ooh, I don't like the sound of that.
This scares me.
Come here.
Got him.
Eh, all this slime is really making me uncomfortable.
I see you there.
Did I just give it a concussion?
It had, like, stars over its head, just like those comics.
Okay, so I've been up here.
Let's just go back.
I feel like there's something in here.
Why is that so black, you know?
I need to investigate.
What do
we got?
All right, it's nothing.
All right.
Cool.
There's a large bone.
That's an...
I saw that just in time.
Got him.
Who else wants some?
I do not want to kill that one.
That's gonna curse the whole area.
Let's go.
Got a magic, dude.
They actually have a decent amount of HP.
Like, look at that.
What the hell is that?
I don't like that.
It's a ghost.
Huh?
I can't kill it.
Here.
Water.
You like that?
How about this?
You can't resist.
That was cool.
But I want this.
You like that one?
Not even the power of Christ compels you, huh?
Well, well, well.
Why is this vibrating like that?
Is this thing gonna damage me when it touches me?
I hope not.
I don't like that.
There's a bunch of enemies.
How do I get rid of this guy?
Wait, is my projectile force field keeping him at bay?
There's no way.
Hold on.
It's not.
Okay, rip.
Oh, no.
I need teleportation one.
Oh, don't hit me.
I'm scared.
Oh, shit.
Oh, no, there's someone of these thingies.
Kill it.
It's making bones.
That's fine.
Give me that.
We're leaving.
I'm so stressed.
What if I go far away quickly enough?
Maybe he'll leave me alone?
I really don't like this dude.
I got a bunch of money, though.
Four thousand six hundred.
I can do something.
There's a... is that a Hymnus jar?
Oh, shit.
Holy crap.
Those things are nuts.
I feel like everything is trying to kill me in here.
This is a very hostile environment.
Okay, at least that big guy is not following me anymore.
That pleases me greatly.
Get rid of that brazier.
See you there.
Oopsie daisy.
We've got a dude down there.
He's dead.
Who else wants some?
Oh, man.
That projectile right there is...
I don't even know.
Unfair.
Someone is pooping.
What the hell is going on there?
The fuck?
Runaway chemical reaction happening.
Wait, this guy is just shooting stuff.
Stop.
420 HP.
What's that?
Acceleration?
Money for me.
Okay.
What's next?
Boink.
Oh, this music is putting me on the edge.
Oh, I can actually fit through here.
Should I?
I can't get in.
So I'm going to do that.
I want to get down here.
The laboratory.
What are we lapping?
What are we experimenting on?
What?
Are you a laboratory man?
Oh, that's acid.
I almost went... no, it's not.
Acid?
Is it?
Why can't I see it?
I think it's toxic sludge, but I'm not going to take the chance.
Oh, God.
Oh, shit.
Man, that even damages them.
That's a wand.
That's going to catch fire now.
Let's be careful.
Man, look at all this temply bullshit here.
That's another black hole looking... not quite a black hole, but almost a black hole.
Looking simple.
Oh, I see, I see.
Stop it.
What else is here?
Okay, there's something shooting an arrow at me.
Decelerating shot.
Makes a projectile decelerate as it flies.
And charm on toxic sludge.
I don't want any of this.
I don't like energy orbs.
I'm good.
Thank you.
Oh,
shit.
I have to remember, I'm immune to the explosion, but not the fire that comes from it.
Uh-oh.
What is that?
Oh, I'm scared.
I think it's time to go back and heal.
Is it though?
Is it time to go back and heal?
I kind of want enough just for one of those wants, you know?
Money wa- The hell?
The fuck just happened?
Everything got cursed.
No, no, no, no, no.
Goddamn.
Oh, there's lava here as well.
That's really bad.
Okay, new plan.
I'm gonna go right instead.
In fact, I don't even know if I'm still in the laboratory, so I'm gonna go this way.
It sort of triggered over here that message, didn't it?
You know what?
I feel like that fire can hurt me later, so let's just get rid of it.
Uh, let's go down here.
Oh, wait.
This is the- Okay.
What?
Where are we?
What is going on?
I want to get in here.
Let's do it the fun way.
Uh, what?
Oink.
Clean it up.
No, no, no.
Don't make him out.
Oh, shit.
It's just the other side.
Okay, okay, okay.
Oh, man.
Oh, wait.
I can- I can do this as well.
Let me do that.
Oh, man.
Okay, that was a sick heal.
Almost full.
What?
Oh, nothing?
There's just a bunch of blood here.
What if I eat all the blood?
Okay.
Whatever.
I'm gonna go the other side.
Very eerie atmosphere here.
What's that?
Oh, I gotta get in there.
Can I lock into a black hole right here?
Oink.
Sick.
Wait a minute.
That works.
What is that?
Crystal.
That's so scary.
Yo.
Looks like a hand.
What's up, bro?
He's coming.
Whoa, what the fuck?
Oh, that looks scary as fuck.
I'm on fire.
Come on.
Yo, this guy's nuts!
Why have I released this?
Why am I doing this?
That's for you!
Enjoy it.
Enjoy that one.
Yeah, you like that?
Here.
Another one.
Eh.
He's stuck.
Uh...
Oink.
Hey, fucker.
I'm so scared of this guy.
He looks like a miniboss.
Oh, he does damage.
He does a lot of it.
What the fuck?
I fucking got you.
I got you, bitch.
Ah, satisfying.
And now I get to have a journal entry about him.
I can read about him.
Makes it all worth it.
Wait, where did I find this guy?
Down here, right?
I want to get up here.
This is the room.
Ah!
You can probably tell I'm a little bit on edge here.
What if I kick this?
Eh!
All right, that's very kickable.
Surprisingly.
All right, good to know.
I can kick that stuff around.
Come on, bring it.
Oh, I see you.
Up tip!
Nice.
Who's next?
I want some.
I hate these traps on the wall.
They scare me.
Can I kick this?
Boink!
Sure can.
Oh, that's all cursed.
That's a, that's a nope from me.
Okay.
Okay, we've been there.
I kind of want to...
release the grains.
The sand.
Oh, wait, we're back here now.
Oh, okay.
Let's go further down.
Keep going down.
That's what I say.
Okay.
Maybe we need a little bit of a grit axis.
Oh!
Wait, what?
Portal to the laboratory.
Is, is that the final area?
This looks very different.
I don't know.
Another one.
Oh!
Oh,
I thought I couldn't damage him.
He looked like a ghost.
Thank God.
Holy shit.
Hold on, I don't want to go through yet.
Obviously, I can't go through yet.
I need to find...
First of all, I got to heal before anything.
The bare minimum.
So I want to explore more to the west first.
Can I?
Almost managed to get through without taking damage there.
Barely.
I need a black hole right now.
Good stuff.
Oh no, this is a dead end.
Almost.
Black hole me.
Oh!
I see you.
Doink!
There's a chest!
Whoa!
Oh, it's that enemy.
He's doing that weird shot.
Haha!
That's actually really cool.
I like that.
Very cool design.
I guess there was just money in that chest.
I'm totally slimed up.
Maximum slime right now.
Wait a minute.
Scorpion.
Dude, is this related to the temple that I found on the surface?
Now that I look at it, it kind of looks similar.
Look at this dude right here.
The one-eyed man.
I wonder how you say the one-eyed man in Finnish.
He has some kind of energy orb and...
Wait a minute.
Are these the alchemists?
He has a potion above his head.
Remember?
We read about the alchemists.
No such thing as halfway crooks?
Laboratory?
It all makes sense.
What are we mixing here, guys?
Hemis.
I am scared of these guys.
Probably the scariest enemy right now.
Yep.
Anything else?
Ah, we've got... Oh no, not again.
I hate that, I hate that, I hate that.
Holy shit.
Come here, come here.
This way.
Sike!
Yeah!
I'm stuck!
I don't know what it is, but I want to kill it.
Grab this, what is it?
Triple spell, large spellable with timer.
Dude, that is a very low rate of fire.
I mean, high rate of fire.
Castile is zero.
Kind of want to try.
Okay, it's not that great.
Oh my god!
Sir?
Change it back.
Thank you.
Man, I'm using my want to traverse.
Actually, sick.
Nope.
Nope, nope, nope, nope, nope.
Nope, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Ah, it goes through the wall, of course.
It's a ghost!
Oh shit!
This is getting too chaotic.
It's not good.
There's a cold nugget on that lamp!
Oh no, cursed rock, cursed rock.
Oh, the audio is bugging.
Okay.
Oh, I'm getting audio glitching right now.
The hell?
Ugh!
Shoot the thing!
I'm fighting for my life here.
Oh, damn.
This is the craziest area yet.
Okay, let's make our way back up.
We gotta heal.
We heal and then we go through the portal.
Heal, through the portal.
So, how do we get up?
Is that gold?
No, that's not gold, that's something else.
Oh man, the audio is...
...crunchy right now.
Why is it like that, I wonder?
Oh, I see a heart!
Is that potion gonna hurt me?
Is that crystal gonna hurt me, I mean...
Ugh!
This is not the way.
This way, I think.
Don't tell me I just came from here.
Up, up, up, up, up, up, up.
This is looking...
...better?
I think.
Let me get through here.
Eh!
Wow, the reverberation on that in these holes.
That sounded awesome.
When you kick that crystal...
Kick that crystal.
When life gets you down, you just gotta kick that crystal.
Very simple.
Just follow those one rules...
...and you will be fine.
Goddamn!
Money!
Hey, there's a guy!
Is he dead?
He's not dead.
Get him!
He died.
Holy blood.
Verta, verta, verta.
Hey!
Awesome.
Oh, I don't like this.
Oh wait, I'm stuck down here.
My wand doesn't work anymore!
I have no more bombs.
Okay, go, go.
We're living, we're living, we're living.
9k gold?
It's time.
How was that?
Some kind of growth I just got rid of.
I don't want to kick that crystal.
That looks like a fragile crystal.
You know what?
Fuck it, kick it.
Gotta kick that crystal.
Okay, I think I'm close to the surface here.
So, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
This is the top.
Definitely.
Get this slime off of me.
Wait.
Wait a minute.
Was it to the right and not left?
It very well could be.
Oh, no, no, no.
Wait, this is it, this is it.
It has to be.
Oh no.
What?
Where?
Ah, here we are.
Nice.
Okay, beautiful.
We made it.
Let's just have a breather here.
Okay.
You know what?
Maybe I'll save my money until the next shop.
Reduce lifetime?
Yeah, I don't know about that.
Is there anything I absolutely want?
Water trail?
I don't think so.
Oh, you know what actually?
This would be kind of cool against the fire enemies, right?
Plasma beam bounce?
I am curious about plasma beam bounce.
But am I 5,850 monies curious?
I'm not sure.
I don't think so.
I'm gonna save my money.
I'll be curious about that one some other time.
Ah, fuck it.
Let's do it.
Let's see what it does.
A projectile launches a plasma beam upon bouncing.
As in, I can dig with it?
Because that would be pretty dope.
That would actually be really sick.
Depends on which direction is this plasma beam being launched.
Also, is it different from the plasma cutter is my immediate question.
I imagine it's still gonna be able to cut through the hardiest of materials given its name.
But who knows?
Okay, we are full HP.
Thanks for looking up.
So let's immediately squander every safe thing we can do and go this way.
Fuck yeah.
Fuck safety.
All gold!
All sick!
There was a lot.
I missed most of it.
Come on, come on.
Yeah, give me that.
Oh, what was that cursed rock?
I see what it is.
Very cool effect when that happens.
The way it just sort of spreads out.
What is that?
I don't like that.
Kick the bone.
Kick the bone into the crystal.
Boink!
Actually hit him for 56 damage.
That's not bad.
Whoa!
What did these guys do even?
Oh, they make sort of sparkly balls.
Get rid of that.
Let me go up here first.
Kick these crystals.
Kick that crystal.
Shoot it.
Curse everything.
Do enemies take damage from the curse, I wonder?
Very good.
So that money I'm not going to be taking because of the curse.
I'm just going to carefully walk around it.
What are you going to do, huh?
I can go up here.
I want to find tablets, damn it.
Give me lore.
Wait, what just happened?
Huh?
What's happening?
He's teleporting me.
I don't enjoy the teleport.
It's confusing to me.
I hate that.
Okay.
Let's go here.
A potion.
Yo, listen to that rumble.
What the fuck?
Water potion.
Oh, sick.
New one.
Is that the lava rumbling like that?
That little pool of lava?
Is there more going on here?
Hmm.
Interesting.
Hamis.
I can't believe there are hamises down here.
Feels like a very unsafe place for them to be.
Because I'm here.
So wait, is there gunpowder inside of these jars, then?
That's got to be it, right?
Oh, shit.
Kick it.
What was that sound?
The hell is that?
Oh, it's one of these guys.
Kill him!
Kill that ball.
Wait, it's acceleration.
Greased lightning.
You feel extremely fast?
Wait, what?
Did he just hit me with some acceleration?
So that's the case.
You can do that some more, sir.
I enjoy it.
Especially when I'm slimed up.
Wait!
There's a number on this!
Hold on.
What?
Wait a minute.
Four!
Say what?
Okay.
That is very...
Why are there stars down here?
Okay, that is very intriguing to me.
Let's remember that.
There's a statue of a wizard looking person with an orb.
With a number four.
Let's see if there's other numbers.
Uh...
Why am I getting boss music?
Or at least what sounds to be boss music?
Goddamn.
The damage.
I'm powerful.
Oh!
That was so satisfying.
Goddamn.
What were those stars?
Oh, here we go.
Uh...
What?
Oh, it's this guy.
Scary stuff.
I've been in there.
Okay.
Dude.
Every single place here is going crazier and crazier.
I wonder if this actually means anything.
I'm getting...
I'm getting... What do you call it?
I had tunic vibes from this right now.
Makes me want to break out a notebook.
And start noting down things.
Especially with the four?
Maybe it just meant, oh, you're on the fourth level, sir.
This is the fourth level of the laboratory.
Or whatever.
Oh, no, not one of these guys.
But I have to kill it, though.
Did I even try to do this?
I can get through here.
Jesus Christ, the slime!
Yo, I just discovered a sick technique.
Check this out.
You fill an area with slime.
You position yourself on the other side of the slime.
With the enemies on the other side, their projectiles won't go through, it seemed like.
But when I shoot, they go through.
Like a one-way street that only helps me.
Look!
Choke point!
Okay, mine also don't go through that well.
Oh, my God.
Those are burning hammers!
I think I'm going to start calling the first area of the hemisphere.
Just because there's so many hammers.
What's in here?
Nothing.
Or a tooth, what is that?
Yeah, it's a bone.
More HP!
Let's go!
My curiosity is rewarded.
I want more of that, by the way.
I want to be rewarded for my cur- Ah!
God damn it.
Wait, what is this?
Polymorphine!
Look how much it glows.
Eh, eh, eh, eh, eh.
Come here.
Sir?
Oh, no, we're doing this dance again.
Heh, heh, heh, heh, heh, heh, heh, heh, heh.
What is this?
Like, it's this craziest projectile he's shooting.
Oh, shit!
Listen to how the music changes when I fight this guy.
I crit him.
Oh, my God!
He's the wildest enemy!
God damn!
Got him!
Oh, wait, I don't take damage from the white explosions.
I guess that makes sense.
I'm immune to explosions.
I just figured, alright, well, cool.
Nice.
There's something in here.
Oh, that was very underwhelming.
That's okay.
Dude, it's frightening!
Cheers, everybody.
I hope you're having a great day.
God damn, that's good.
Mmm!
Okay, there's a metal and blood there.
That's cool.
I can dig it.
Actually, I can't, because I don't have digging capabilities.
I can't do the two cymbals and a drum or whatever.
Two drums and a cymbal.
With my mouth, I just can't.
I don't have the ability, sir.
We have a dude!
Excuse me, do you have a dude license to be dooting like that?
Uh-oh.
Oh, that's another one of those guys.
That's not good.
Cursed Rock, that's also not good.
How am I gonna get through this, dude?
I don't think I am gonna get through.
I have nothing left down here.
Oh, hello.
Didn't even see you there.
Okay, you know what?
I'm gonna make my way back to the portal that I saw.
And we're going through.
So I came from here.
And then we just gotta go down.
But let me also keep an eye out for numbers.
Okay, so this is number four.
Wait, I kinda wanna get in here!
Is there no way for me to get in?
I can't believe I haven't found the digging wand.
That was like the whole thing I wanted to do in this place.
Find a digging wand.
And then go up towards the hemisphere.
I wonder if...
You know what?
Maybe the crystal, the...
This one will actually explode the wall, let's see.
Oh!
Hello!
Axe is acquired, baby.
Ingenuity at its best.
Smart.
Very cool.
This is just an empty room.
Oh, I don't like that.
Water me, water me, water me.
Ah, okay.
Boo!
I'm scared.
Come here.
Weird spells they have.
Look at that.
Another simple... Oh, what's happening here?
Okay, it's not quite the same type of deal here.
This is number four up there.
Look at this stuff here!
I wonder if any of this has any meaning.
Oh!
You bastard!
You caught me off guard there.
I'm just gonna lead up there, okay.
Wait, I can probably get through over here, no?
Ow!
Fucking hell.
I hate when I get polymorphed.
I'm super vulnerable.
Come on.
Eh.
Thank you.
Scary stuff.
I can get through here as well.
Nice.
Oh, I don't like the fire there.
Yeah, that's gonna set fire to all that flammable gas.
What do we have here?
I made it to the other side of the wall.
X.
Did he die?
I don't think he died.
Yo, this place is massive!
Next!
Okay.
Oh, look at this dude!
Look!
Why is he waiting there?
It's like he...
Oh, shit.
Like he can't get to me in my circle here sometimes.
But other times he can.
It's a bit weird.
Dead end.
Shit.
Who knows?
Maybe they're not even dangerous.
Maybe they're not even gonna damage me.
But I'm not here to find out.
How can I circumvent you?
Come here.
Wait, what?
Oh, wait, did I just use a different wand?
Oh!
I didn't mean to use that wand.
I was kind of afraid what it would do, but...
There we go.
Accidentally used it.
Dead end.
Fucking kill everyone.
Kill them all!
Grab the gold!
Oh my god, no, all the gold!
That was sick!
Kill it!
Yo, that has a lot of HP!
Oh, I hate this!
Nope, nope, nope, nope!
He's not gonna let me pass!
Holy shit!
Yo, wait, where am I going?
I'm ascending!
Is he alive?
I think I got him.
Where am I going?
What the hell...
is...
Just happened.
That's acceleration!
What the fuck is going on up here?
Hello?
Oh, I thought those were worms!
What's that?
Wait.
Wait a minute.
Oh...
I see.
Wait.
Did that spider dig all the way down?
That's fucking crazy that is simulated while I'm doing things down there!
Is everything simulated at all times?
What the fuck?
Am I really here?
What the shit?
No.
Oh my...
We made it back up, boys!
We can make it to the surface!
Heck yeah!
That's awesome!
Looks like... hemispheres back on the menu, boys!
And I've been here.
Everything's explored.
Why am I doing this?
Water me!
Yeah, you know what?
No, no, fuck that.
We're just gonna go up.
Fuck all that noise.
Take me this way.
What the hell's that?
Wait!
Can I... can I make wands here?
Does that still work?
Hold on.
There's no way.
This was the water bath.
Oh no, wait, this has collapsed.
Ah, but wait a minute.
Where was the hole?
Ah!
Wait a minute.
Let's see here.
Maybe I do want one of these.
I want a non-shuffle wand.
Oh wait, I can't... I can't edit anyway.
That's the thing.
But maybe I'll do this anyway, just to get a non-shuffle.
I don't know if I want this one.
So I'm keeping this wand because of this bloodlust spell here.
It seems insane, but it's also dangerous, so maybe I shouldn't do it.
Because I'm kind of deep in this run, you know?
So maybe I'll just replace it...
with digging stuff?
Hey!
I mean, it works in a pinch.
It's not great by any means.
But it works.
Unfortunately, it's shuffle again.
But it can dig.
Actually, hold on, before I go on, let me see if there's any other wand here that can also dig.
Just to cover all my bases.
There's that.
I forgot what that was.
No, I think I'm good.
I don't think there's anything here.
Okay.
So I remember that to the east of here...
there is a little path.
And you'll see what I mean.
Watch this.
Maybe this is not the right area, but...
I believe somewhere over here.
Hey, what's up, guys?
What the hell?
Where did you come from?
I thought I cleared this part.
Here we go.
Look.
There it is.
Haha, steel trap, motherfucker.
Oh, yeah.
I have been here.
And now we're in the jungle.
What does this want?
It comes back to me!
It's back in my hands.
Oh, that's amazing.
This is where I killed the thing inside the egg.
Oh, yeah.
We are so back.
So we actually got to get to the snowy depths.
The snowy region.
And then we can get from there all the way up to the hemisphere.
Blow that one up.
Let me actually just explore it a little bit.
That's one of the best parts about this game.
Just explore some shit.
Who knows?
Maybe there's a heart here that I missed.
Also, there's...
Wait, maybe this is the region where I can still edit my wand.
Yo.
I really hope that it's not like a...
If I break one holy mountain, is it going to affect every previous?
You know what I mean?
We'll have to see.
So the question is, is it west or east of here?
That's like the big queue on my brain right now.
I think it's here actually.
I remember this.
Here it is.
Fuck yeah.
Oh, tell me.
Wait.
Oh my god!
We get to make wands!
Oh, look how cheap these spells are!
What is that over there?
Why is that glowing?
There's something glowing there.
You see that?
The hell?
Yo.
Okay, let's see here.
What do we have?
Plasma beam bounce.
How about we try this?
Let's put that on a magic arrow.
Oh, wait a minute.
Oh wait, that's not cutting through anything.
Not that I can tell at least.
No.
It is...
Okay, so...
Okay.
Plasma beam is not the same as...
Plasma cutter, obviously.
It's not the same spell, but...
It does not cut, it seems.
Interesting.
Gotcha.
I do want plasma cutter, but maybe on a different wand.
Plasma cutter, it costs 40 mana.
Okay.
Let me do this.
That better?
Oh, recharge is shit on this.
Oh wait, I can reduce recharge.
Maybe I have something that can reduce recharge.
Or I can do...
Double scatter spell.
Wait, I have an idea.
Trigger?
So, this shoots two at a time.
Oh wait, let me...
Do I have another wand somewhere here?
Did I leave some behind?
But I mean, I guess I saw a wand down there.
Man, it feels kind of cozy being back here.
Feels nice.
This wand right here, what is that?
It's a shuffle wand.
Right.
I mean, I can use this one, maybe.
Let me see.
1,620 mana.
If I now do...
I just want a more efficient cutter here.
Watch this.
Ouch!
Wait a minute.
No, it's not doing what I thought it would.
So what I'm thinking is, it shoots one at a time, right?
This one is being shot, then it shoots energy orb with a trigger.
And the trigger, when it impacts, or like when it has a collision, it's going to wrap to this one and grab this, right?
Because this one has a trigger.
So I thought this would maybe...
circumvent the recharge time on this.
But wait, is that even the issue?
It is the issue.
Maybe not, then.
What if I do this?
What happens then?
Okay.
I want to make a really efficient digging mechanism, basically.
Lava to blood.
Hell, yo, actually, wait a minute.
Dude, I know what I'm going to do.
We're going back up to the hemisphere, right?
I remember a lake of lava.
Let's see how well this works.
What are we talking here?
Are we talking one impact and everything gets turned?
That could be sick.
If that's the case, we'll have to see at least.
Hold on, I also have a bunch of other spells, don't I?
What's that?
Concentrated explosion?
Limits the radius of a projectile's explosion heavily.
Oh, that would be pretty cool on the holy bomb, no?
Actually, there's something I want to test here.
I think I have some black holes over here.
I want to see what the deal is with the slow speed of it.
So if I go down here and grab a couple of these...
Oh, they're empty.
What about these ones?
So if I put this on that wand instead, is there a difference?
It's still slow.
Okay.
So what if I...
Ah, man, I wish I had the speed spell.
You know?
That one would be amazing.
Unless I do...
What if we do the...
Wait, delayed spell cast?
No.
Double scatter.
Magic bolt with timer.
No, not timer.
I want the other one.
Trigger.
So if I do this...
It's going to do exactly where it impacts, no?
Ah, but then it bounces off like that.
That's weird.
I want it to keep going.
Shit.
Okay.
I mean, I can technically just replace some of these.
Right?
And put this on another wand, obviously.
So how about we put it on...
Maybe this stays like that.
This one is... goes there.
Uh...
I don't know.
Maybe I get rid of that one.
There we go.
This one I kind of want to keep.
Let's get rid of this one.
I don't like that.
Rid of some of these.
What do we have over here?
Glowing lands and stuff.
Eh.
I don't know.
This is a mess with all the spells here, by the way.
This is a complete mess.
That needs to be there.
It needs to be here.
And these go here.
Ah, but then I don't have a lot of slots.
God damn it.
I could put them here, but then it shoots two at a time.
I don't want that either.
Fuck.
This is like a mess, isn't it?
I hate it.
Honestly, I don't know what I want.
I'll just leave it like this.
Fuck it.
Let's get a bomb.
Put it there.
What is this?
Explosion of spirits?
Oh, like alcohol, right?
An inebriating explosion.
Okay.
On this one down here, I'm going to put that one.
Let's put it on that one.
Let's see.
If I find some lava, this should...
Oh, wait.
It casts two spells.
That means it...
I don't know if this is doing what I think it does, then.
Because of the two spells.
Let's do this instead.
There.
That's better.
Makes any lava within a projectile's range turn into blood.
Oh, okay.
You know what?
How about we do...
this instead.
How much mana is that going to leave me?
Okay, I go Umm instantly.
What if I replace it like that?
I still go Umm instantly.
We need these here.
Absolutely need them.
Is there anything I could replace?
Maybe I can replace...
What is a good projectile to use here?
Honestly, for now, keep it like this.
That's what I say.
Fireball Orbit.
I want some more of these.
Is that the empty one?
It is.
It's a full one?
What about this one?
Empty?
I don't know.
Let's just move on.
I mean, we have a plasma thingy.
We can technically cut our way through.
The only problem is...
to get out of here efficiently.
Whoops.
Right.
That's the second time I've done that today.
Oh!
Look at that!
That means the portal is right.
Oh, it's actually right up there then.
It's going to take a while.
Here's what I'm going to do.
I'm going to make a little tunnel so I can go like this.
So I don't have to fly every time.
I don't know any other way to get through here.
Do I stand like there now?
Oh, that's not too bad actually.
Sick!
This run has become something, isn't it?
Incredible.
Ah!
Come on.
I can hear it.
Oh, I'm super low on mana.
Oh my god, look at the mana.
Oh, that's slow.
Whoops.
Did not consider that!
Yikes!
But it's right up there, I can make it.
This needs to be a little efficient here with my clicks.
Wait a minute.
Yeah, that is definitely it.
Oh, I got a heart attack.
These things are scary.
I knew that was going to happen at some point.
Come on.
I'm cutting through the text.
This is actually so cool that I can do this.
Nice.
Look at that shit.
We made it.
We're fucking back.
Oh, what do we have here?
Hey, I remember this one!
A chaotic path.
Giga disc projectiles.
I think this one's dangerous.
And that was a missile.
Just straight up missile.
Pretty cool.
Just go straight up.
Oh, and here we are, look at that.
How amazing is this?
The question is...
Oh, wait a minute, how do I...
Oh, actually, there's stuff over there.
Maybe I should just do this.
Shit, I should have done it here.
Whoops.
I forgot there was a bomb in there.
There we go.
So...
I should try some of these actually.
Electric charge.
Avoiding arc.
Propane tank.
Delayed.
I want this.
I still can't edit things though, that's unfortunate.
I don't want this.
I don't think I want this either.
Give me that.
Oil.
Light.
Blood mist.
Avoiding arc.
Makes the projectiles shy away from obstacles.
Hmm...
I feel like that would mess with my aim, no?
Doesn't seem very good.
Okay.
If we can go one higher from here, we should be in the snowy area.
And then we can go to the right and there should be a way up.
Oh, and then I know exactly where to go to find something very special.
I'm going to do it right...
I wonder if it's the same spot every time.
Yeah, I'm hearing it.
I hear it.
Let's do this again.
This is a little tedious.
But I'm way too curious.
I'm making my way up there no matter what.
I have things to explore, dammit.
I'm going to be conservative here with my mana.
Nice.
In fact, what if I just stand in one spot like this and dig up and then just fly up?
I wonder if there's enough room.
Hey, wait a minute.
Hey, that's totally how I should do it.
That works.
That works wonders.
Holy shit, that goes far.
Yo, that's way better.
Look at that!
Yeah!
Much better.
I have returned, people!
Have you missed me?
Actually, everything is empty here, right?
Because I killed it.
Oh, never mind.
Look at these cute enemies now.
Probably don't care about collecting money here.
I want to go east.
Just go east.
Oh, shit.
Nice.
Oh, wait, that's a...
No?
All right, what if I do this?
See ya.
Look how cute these enemies are.
They're just tickling me.
Wait.
No, it's got to be up here.
It's up and right, I believe.
Here we go, here we go.
This is it.
Now watch this.
Ah!
Wait a minute.
I'm going to listen here.
Here, you hear it?
Here.
Reveal thyself to me.
Oh, yeah, it's getting louder.
Wait.
Is it above me?
I think I hear it above me.
Oh!
Fuck.
Why do I get such a fright from that, God damn it?
There it is.
Found it.
It's the missile again.
You discovered an orb of true knowledge.
Secrets of utter destruction have been unlocked to you.
Okay.
How about we get rid of that?
A nuke.
Fuck.
Okay, a nuke.
I like it.
75 damage.
250 explosion.
That's not that crazy, is it?
200 mana?
One use?
Wait, what does this say?
Heat my warning, or death and decay will follow.
Oh, yeah?
What does thou mean with these words?
Get rid of that one.
Oh, wait, what am I doing?
Grab it.
And then...
get rid of that one.
Let's try this.
Oh!
It totally works.
Look at that.
Oh, that's scary, actually.
This is going to lead to the big pool of lava, isn't it?
I almost ran into it.
Yeah, it is.
Okay.
Pretty cool.
Dude, I'm going to try and kill the boss here.
I don't have full HP, but that's fine.
I have a lot of HP.
I should be nuking this boss now.
Actually, I can't.
Technically.
But you know what I mean.
I'm going to nuke him with my machine gun.
Konekiveri.
There we go.
The bridge has been systroid.
Okay, this is it.
Let's fucking go.
It's still the same, right?
Transportation of metals.
Thank you!
Okay, let's get ready.
How are we going to do this?
Actually, I don't have much choice.
It's just to shoot him.
Actually, no, no, no.
I can go invisible.
I also have acceleration I could use.
Let's be super fast.
Here we go.
Super fast and inviciblium.
Kind of want to turn this into inviciblium only.
Let's see here.
It doesn't quite work like that.
But you know what I can do?
Is I can sort of do this.
Ah, stop!
Oh my god.
Ah shit.
Wait, what?
My inviciblium is gone.
Oh no, I must have done something.
Ah crap.
Alright, let's try it.
Hey bitch!
Whoa, wait, how do you have so much HP?
I mean, how do I do so little damage is what I meant to say.
Wait, what the fuck is he?
Whoops.
I feel like I should not fight him, I'm scared.
Okay, he's here.
He's here.
I'm leaving, I'm leaving.
Fuck you, fuck you.
Oh, that's novel.
Phew!
Okay, you know what, fuck that shit.
No, no, no, no, no.
I'm scared.
For some reason, he took no damage and I don't understand why.
I'm going to the top.
Straight to the top, baby.
Whoops.
Look at us, we're back at the beginning, man.
That's the bridge!
I remember this bridge.
That's a nice bridge.
Nice.
Fuck you.
Okay, so the quest... where do we want to go, man?
The world is our oyster!
I can technically go anywhere...
Actually, I can go up here too, look.
Whoa!
I'm back.
The fact that I can go back like this is awesome.
Let's put this here.
Let's see if this one does anything.
I'm stuck.
The fuck?
Hey!
Oh, that wasn't that much.
I was like, I thought I would get something new, maybe.
Okay.
Cool.
Let's explore.
Dude, I'm so ready to fuck some shit up up here.
It's going to be glorious.
It's so quiet up here.
There's no enemies.
It's so quaint.
Until I came along.
Whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop.
Hold on.
I can kick this.
Haha.
That's all?
This reminds me of...
Twin Peaks.
That's nice.
I love that.
Wait, that is Twin Peaks.
I know.
Sounded like it.
Oh, man, I want that running all the time.
Can I just not have that on me?
I want a boombox real bad.
Look how big this wand is that I'm carrying.
It's bigger than my character.
Extra health, one off.
This was sick.
That gave me like 400 HP or something.
Maybe even a...
Oh!
Oh, right.
I was ready for that.
I entered the desert.
The air feels hot.
What?
Boss?
Where?
Wait.
Is that... that's the same boss?
What the hell?
Where is he?
External ratio.
Run!
We're leaving.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
We don't like that.
Oh, but we do like this.
Okay, the boss thing is gone.
Thank God.
Look at this.
Ain't no problem when I've got plasma cutter.
I have arrived, bitches.
Show me your fortunes.
Look at this place.
It's the exact same theme as that area I was in just before.
Yeah, and it's the same jars.
Well, almost.
Even this place, even the...
I don't even know the pieces here look similar.
It is definitely the same place, but like not the same place.
You know what I mean?
Like a huge pyramid.
Pyramid.
Research notes?
Wait.
What?
Hold on, I'm scared.
What is that thing right there?
That scares me.
I fucking knew something was going to happen.
Call me Selmin Koi-P.
Come here.
I'm going to fuck you up, bitch.
Maybe not.
Maybe I'm definitely not going to fuck you up.
It takes no damage.
Where'd you go?
Whoa!
All right, all right, all right, all right.
Calm down.
Man, everything bounces off him.
Oh, I hit him.
I think I need to hit a weak spot or something.
Where are you?
He's up there to the left.
Come here, sir.
Shit.
Somehow I damaged him.
I'm not sure how.
Oh, wait, he opens his mouth or something, and then I can shoot him.
I saw that briefly.
Look how everything bounces off of him.
But then sometimes they don't.
There, you see?
He's open.
Oh, I got him.
I got you.
Oh, my God.
Dropping all kinds of things.
I want.
With rocks.
Fire arcs.
Between them.
All right.
What's that?
Cannot copy random spell.
Copy random spell?
Get rid of...
Maybe that one.
What's that one?
Nala.
Give another hand with snala.
Let's see.
The duration of a projectile is set to zero?
Say what?
Oh, wait, I can't do anything here yet.
Let me also get rid of that one.
And that one.
Fuck those.
Copy random spell.
Copy three random spells.
Oh, wait, there's a bunch of stuff.
Get rid of that one.
Random static projectile spell.
Cast one random?
That seems a bit crazy.
Okay.
Very cool.
And he dropped the wand as well.
That's awesome.
Do I want it?
I don't think I do.
I'm going to leave that there for now.
All right, been here, done that.
Wait, did I heal somehow?
Wait a minute.
Okay, I must have...
Okay, so I thought I picked up the ones that just increased my health.
But I must have picked up something that healed me.
Okay.
Okay, hold on.
Before I go on...
I gotta read.
Where did it go?
Look, it's all bloody.
Okay, one in the pond.
One in the tree.
One on the ledge.
One under the sun.
Okay.
One on the ledge.
Could be referring to the musical instruments.
There is one in the pond, right?
I think there is one in the tree.
One under the sun.
Hold on.
Let me get my notebook, actually.
It's actually notebook time.
Okay, here we go.
I'm just gonna write this down.
One in the pond.
One in the tree.
One on the ledge.
Which ledge?
One under the sun.
I think it has to be referring to the musical instrument because...
the pond can only be referring to that big pool of water, right?
It's gotta be.
And what do we have in there?
We have that weird musical instrument.
Maybe I need to play them all.
You know?
That's the first thought I have.
Play them all.
Or activate them all.
Okay, so one on the ledge.
One under the sun.
What could that mean?
It could mean...
I don't know.
Which ledge, though, are we talking about?
Maybe there's a ledge very east of here somewhere.
Or maybe west of here.
Ah, stop that.
I just had a mini burp.
I apologize for that.
Got him.
Man, I kinda wanna go back and kill that boss.
In the hemisphere.
What if he drops lore?
Gotcha.
Can I eat sand?
Weird question to ask, I know, but...
Oh, stop it.
Look at all this sand out here.
I wish I could eat it all.
Fuck you.
Dude, this is awesome.
This is like a whole new area.
I think it's definitely intended to explore this after you explore at least the frozen place.
Why does everything look so weird and...
I don't even know, like, look at all these holes.
Almost looks like...
it's rotted away or something, the material.
The hell?
That's a heezy man.
Sand cave!
Hello!
Oh, fill up the water bottle.
In fact, let's have three water bottles.
There we go.
Lots of water.
We can't run out of water now.
Can I cut through here?
Yes, I can.
The music just jump-scared me.
I like it.
Oh, wait, they're shooting each other.
Hello.
What's up, man?
Wait.
I'm not done with this area.
We gotta explore absolutely everything.
I need to find musical instruments.
One on the ledge.
Oh, shit, this guy's shooting charm.
Is that bad at all?
Is it good?
I guess I don't know.
Probably don't want to get hit by it.
Just to be safe.
Look at this guy hanging out.
Happy Friday, bitch.
All right, cheers, everybody.
God damn, that's good.
I was parched.
You're not feeling when you drink something and you're really parched.
And you get tears in your eyes because it's so beautiful.
I get it all the time.
It's a beautiful moment that needs to be appreciated.
Give me more tablets.
I am actually like insanely intrigued by the research notes.
What is that?
Excuse me?
What if I touch it?
It hurts me.
Wait, what?
It's a sonar beep.
Is it trying to guide me?
What's happening?
Hello?
Oh.
That's a weird evil spirit.
Anyway, what I was about to say is the research notes.
Who's research?
Right?
And it's like the first time in this game that I'm getting something a little concrete out of the lore.
I feel like I have a sort of a mission here.
For the first time.
Ow!
I never learn.
Come here.
Cut through.
I hit myself.
What was that?
He just hit me.
I swear, I'm gonna kill myself with that plasma cutter one day.
It's gonna happen.
You know it, I know it, everybody knows it.
Shoot it.
Ham is inside.
Why are there heezy people here?
Dude, maybe the heesians were trying to do research here.
I mean, they seem civilized, right?
They have fucking cafeterias and bunk beds and what have you.
And they seem to be here on a mission too, in like little expedition parties.
Now we're back in the sand cave.
That's fine, let's check out the sand cave, let's blow that up.
Nice.
Before we go through there, I wanna check everything up here.
Uh...
Is that a wand?
Nope, it's a ghostbuster.
Oh, ow, ow, ow.
So many.
Yo guys, what's happening?
What are you doing in these parts?
Why did you come all the way up here?
Damn, some eerie music.
Ow, no wait, I'm okay.
Explosions are fine.
Sir, will you stop that?
Oh, good thing I'm immune.
I'm bumping geese.
Okay, we've been there.
We've been there too.
Now we go down.
Again, fire is number one enemy.
I can't believe how good this wand is that I made.
It's been so good for so long.
I almost recalled myself into the plasma cutter.
Damn.
Maybe they're like archaeologists or something.
Wait, what am I affected by?
I'm poisoned.
Oh no.
I'm losing way too much HP here.
This is not sustainable.
Especially because I don't know when I'll be able to heal again.
Not like I have a holy mountain to look forward to here.
At least I don't think so.
But I'm really hoping to be surprised about that.
This is fun.
Definitely making my way through here.
That's right.
Come here.
Wait,
what is that?
Dude, I am so immersed in this game.
This is incredible.
Oi.
Oh, I can shoot the projectile, of course.
I did not think about... Ooh, that's a lot of fire.
What the hell?
It's an oil fire.
That explains a lot.
I'm trying to listen for secrets inside the rock.
Maybe the walls will speak to me.
Sing to me, brother Feltbar.
Sing to me.
Dude, where am I going?
Dicks.
The suspense is killing me.
Okay, so I have walked all the way along the right edge now.
And I'm at the bottom.
Dead end.
But I can get through here.
Water.
Hello.
Oh, shit.
I'm poisoned.
This is actually really bad.
Bro, the poison is a killer.
Holy shit.
Wow, that takes a lot of HP.
Do not get poisoned.
Fuck me.
You really gotta take care of that quick.
Poison scares me.
What is that?
Is that poison, fumes?
Can I be okay?
Drain that water.
Those guys are the ones with the poison.
Wow, what a shot.
Okay, go here.
Let's see.
If they have green guns, they shoot poison.
I think that's the rule.
Why is the screen shaking?
That makes me nervous.
Wow, he hit me somehow.
Oh, someone shoots poison up there.
It's you, it's you.
Oh, fuck you, fuck you so much.
Oh, man, get rid of it.
I'm gonna die to poison.
Oh, no, oh, no, no, man.
Fuck you.
The fate of my existence.
Oh, another one of those guys.
Poison everywhere.
Another one.
Got him.
I feel like I maybe want to leave.
I want to go to the ledge.
I want to go to under the sun.
Oh, Jesus, holy crap.
God damn.
This place does not fuck around.
Okay, I'm going to go outside again.
Because think about it.
Hold on.
One in the pond, one in the tree.
One on the ledge, one under the sun.
That all seems to me like it's upstairs.
None of that suggests it's down here.
A ledge could mean down here.
There could be a ledge on the ground, I guess.
But to me, a ledge sounds more like something up there, you know?
Let's go.
Let's try and go this way and find the exit over here.
Is that a dead hymns?
What was that?
Not all that blood.
Something shook.
Wait a minute.
What's up here?
Ah, okay.
I have been right here.
Okay, I think we're at the edge.
So we got to go further up.
I mean, I could just cut my way through, I guess, if I really wanted, but I can just go up here.
Because I did find my way in, so I can go out again the same way.
I made this hole.
Here we go.
There it is.
Ah, fresh air.
What a nice breeze it is.
Cheers, everybody.
Happy Friday.
Let's go on top of the pyramid.
What?
Oh!
Hello!
The necessity of concealing the art is one of the chief anxieties of alchemists.
I read this one before.
We are sworn to secrecy by heaven and earth and hell.
By the four elements.
By the height and the depth.
By Hermes, by Anubis, and by the howlings of Kirkros.
An oath has been required of us to reveal nothing clearly to any uninitiated being.
I believe I'm very uninitiated.
What does this down here mean?
What if I cut it?
Uh...
All right.
I'm taking that.
Actually, is there anything above me here?
Maybe I can put the tablet somewhere up here on a floating island?
I'm going to the moon, boys.
Take me.
Oh!
Hey!
I fucking knew it!
There is something!
Answer the cloudscape!
What?
Oh, shit.
Dude, I can stand the... I can stand the cloud!
Oh, hello.
Oh, my God.
Dude, these enemies don't fuck around.
Uh-oh.
Oh, that guy's mean.
We're leaving!
Nah, fuck that shit.
Fuck that shit.
I'm going down again.
That seems insane.
Oof.
Huh?
What just happened?
It looked like I got teleported for a second.
Whoo!
Okay, I almost died there.
That guy took my HP real quick.
You know what?
That's pretty fucking cool that there's something up there.
Oh.
Heaven and hell.
That's the heaven.
Maybe I entered heaven.
I actually forgot... Oh, cloudscape is what it said, right?
Cloudscape.
The hell?
Could that be the ledge?
Could that be one under the sun?
Under the sun?
In the clouds?
Right under the sun?
That could be it, actually.
Maybe there's a musical instrument up there.
Man, what is this thing?
What if I do this?
My essence eater.
I don't understand this.
Isn't eating any of my essences?
Boom.
So you can do that.
Something tells me there's something else to be done with those things.
Yeah.
Guess we'll figure that out later.
There's a scale here.
I saw this one before.
Is there anything below?
Oh!
Fucking hell, Oliver.
I hate myself.
I should not use that weapon.
It's not meant for me.
I'm not certified.
I'm just not...
Watchtower.
That's right!
I was here, remember?
This was one of the very first things I did.
When I started this game, I went here.
And I don't remember why I went back.
Did I just hear a bell?
Singing bowls.
So hold on, watchtower?
Watching over what?
And who is watching?
Oh, that's right, I remember this now.
Okay, there's definitely something in there.
Here's the plan, here's the plan.
I'm not certified to use this laser, but that's okay.
I'm gonna do it anyway.
Oh, you know, I could drain it.
Hold on, let me go to the top first.
Yeah, I'm gonna drain it.
We're draining that bitch.
And then we'll see what's in there.
I'm so excited.
I'm gonna drain it here so it floats down this way.
Oh!
Motherfucker!
It was waiting for me.
I know it was.
Why does nothing else flow?
Wait, what?
There's something up there blocking it.
Volcanic rock.
Oh no, what's happening?
Is there steam?
The steam is...
Steam is turning it into volcanic rock.
But I guess I can do this.
Yo, that's interesting.
Okay, so I can sort of just...
Be careful, be careful, be careful.
Some lava gets through.
Wait,
what the fuck is that?
Wait a minute.
What the hell?
The...
Lava to blood.
That's what's happening.
Holy shit.
The game just revealed to me what I just found on my own.
It's saying pond.
The cloud.
One in the pond.
One in the tree.
One on the ledge.
I still don't understand the ledge.
One under the sun.
This has to be one under the sun.
It has to be.
Oh man.
I gotta go to the pond again.
That's fucking cool.
I'm low on HP though.
Actually, I just cut my way out.
But actually, I don't want to cut my way out just yet.
I want to go to the very bottom of this watchtower.
And see what's down there.
I do not remember.
Oh, that's lava.
Seems like a lot of it too.
I mean, I could turn it into blood.
But why would I do that?
When I can do this.
Ooh, listen to that rumble.
That's some shit, ain't it?
What?
How did that affect that?
Oh, don't hit it.
So scary.
Okay, I'm not so sure about this right now.
Let's stick to this exploration of the musical instruments.
Ah, you know what?
I could also keep going east.
Ah, okay.
You know what?
I'm going to keep going east.
And then we're going to circle back to the lake.
I wonder if the music is still on there.
After I turned it on.
I wish I could bring it with me and have music everywhere.
Oh.
This one could be the one under the sun.
You know?
Oh, the desert.
Under the sun.
That could be what that means.
You know, when you're out in the desert, you're under the sun.
It just means there's no clouds.
It's all sunny all the time.
Whoops.
Yeah.
Okay, let's just vibe out with this for a while.
Oh, yeah.
Cool.
That's two.
I'm going to assume this is the one under the sun.
Also, what is down below here?
Look at this hand.
Oh, wait, this just looks like dense rock.
Okay, nice rock music going on there.
I do like the other sound better, though.
The Twin Peaks one.
Wait, is it getting night?
Look how dark it is.
Why is it so dark?
Hello?
Dude, this area makes me have that feeling with the pooping.
This is triggering it.
Extremely dense rock.
It's got to be something up here.
Yo!
Another one of these.
There's a...
There's a spell in there.
And I can see it.
Interesting.
Remember that area we found in...
Was it...
The...
I think it was in the snowy region in the west.
It was also question marks.
It was in the dark area.
Actually, similar to how this place is dark.
Oh, essence...
What?
Hold on.
Let me also get rid of one thing.
Maybe this one.
I have so many of them.
Essence of Earth.
Your being...
Your being releases damaging light.
Oh, wait.
Oh!
Oh.
Oh, no.
Wait, is this constant?
Dude.
Is that an explosion?
I guess that's great because I'm immune to that.
Holy shit!
Thank God, huh?
I guess we're doing this.
Weird.
What?
Okay.
That's gonna be weird.
Wait, I kind of want to go on top of this.
Wait just...
Wait, what the fuck is going on?
Oh, wait, I forgot I can do this.
I make fireworks.
Here we go!
To the top.
Oh, what?
Your being able to fly infinitely is actually insane.
Oh, shit!
Oh, shit, I guess we made it back up here.
Run!
Oh, it's a cloud.
Oh, shit!
I can't cut my way through.
Wow, clouds are very immune to plasma?
Guess I'm going this way.
Fuck all of y'all.
Fuck your rules.
I'm going up here, man.
Man, that thing is annoying, actually.
Ooh!
Hello!
Oh, shit, I can't read it because of this thing.
Oh, wait, wait a minute.
I gotta...
throw that shit away.
Tome of essences.
The four essences represent the four elements that formed this visible world.
Imbued with their terrible power, one may do great deeds.
But one should be afraid of their destructive might.
To this end, we have devised a way to remove these dangerous forces.
Seek it in the west and east.
A legend also tells that all the elements originated from the egg of sky and returned to it one day.
Dude.
Okay, east and west?
Coral chest?
How do I get in?
Sir?
Hey!
I can't open it.
Maybe I need to use stronger measures.
Come on, open up!
Ooh!
Uh...
Methinks the chest went in the black hole.
Whoops.
Hopefully nothing valuable was inside of there.
Oh well.
Oh, what the hell is that now?
Hello?
I feel like I should not be here.
What?
What's happening?
Man, some of them do some kind of spell on me.
That's super confusing.
No, I don't like this.
I don't like this.
We're leaving.
Oh no, I'm stuck.
Money me.
I kind of want to kill that thing.
Release us a bunch of gold.
Okay, yeah.
Neat.
Wait, what?
Kill him.
Whoa, stuck!
I'm stuck!
Jesus!
I'm on fire!
Holy shit, this guy's insane!
He did.
Okay, we're leaving.
We're leaving this place.
We're done here.
Fucking hell.
What a mess.
This game is nuts.
Hello!
Oh!
I was stuck.
I think he froze me.
All right.
Cool.
All right, I'm gonna... Fuck, this spell is annoying me, man.
Your being releases damaging light.
I hate that.
With a passion right now.
Okay.
Well, I'm gonna go west, I guess.
In fact, I'm gonna go to that pond slash lake.
And check what's right above it.
I think it's just the cloud, but...
Let's just double check that.
Cheers.
Honestly, even if I died now, I would be happy.
This was a great run.
You know?
Also, what's going on there?
Oh!
Oh, shit!
I may have spoken too soon with the whole ending the run now.
I am scared.
Nah, we're leaving.
Fuck you!
That thing can't take damage?
I don't understand that boss.
Maybe it has a similar mechanic where you need to...
Whoa, has it been digging all of this?
No fucking way!
That thing's a menace!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Whoa-ho!
Yeah!
Is the music still on?
It's not on.
Music is on.
Let's go try and go on above the... place here.
We're just gonna get to the cloud again, right?
Notice how the background changes too.
Hello!
Uh, there's an arrow pointing right.
What the hell?
Oh, wait, do I want to go down there?
Oh, wait, what?
It's draining.
Whoa!
Color me intrigued.
Arrow to the left?
West and east?
Oh, here we go.
Ah!
Fuck!
Milk potion.
Uh...
Okay.
I guess I want to bring some.
Let's take some milk.
Bro, this explosion thing on me is pissing me off.
There we go, empty.
Milk me up!
Wait, what?
Nice, it is working.
I got the milk.
I got the milk!
You know what's gonna be dangerous with this effect on me?
If I'm near explosives, it's gonna blow shit up.
I have a bad feeling about this.
Music is good though.
Ominous...
temple.
Okay, okay.
That's how I could have entered?
What is that?
Ominous liquid?
Wait a minute, haven't I seen this ominous liquid before?
It damages me, right?
Let's double check.
Wait, what?
Oh, yeah, oh, yeah, something's... Oh, wow, it's happening!
Huh?
Yeah, it's definitely damaging me.
200 HP, man, this is soon over.
That's fine.
It was a good run.
Let's see what we got down here.
Okay, that's it, huh?
So we could have entered from the bottom too.
That is very interesting.
Why is this so mysterious?
Why is this so ominous?
This must be a very rare liquid or something.
What if I put milk on it?
Milk it up!
Interesting, what if I mix it?
Okay, let's keep going west.
Very interesting.
What?
I kind of want to see what's in the middle of this.
Oh, wait, there's nothing in there.
I'm accidentally chopping down all the trees.
I'm so sorry.
I don't mean to.
You know what?
I actually kind of want to remove all this ice.
I want to see what's inside of here.
What is hiding beneath this ice?
You know what I mean?
There's got to be something here.
Do I have any holy... I do have a holy thing.
Let's lodge this in here.
Whoa!
Sick.
Wait, is there something?
Maybe not, okay.
It was worth a try, I would say.
Okay, so we have done one in the pond.
I think we have done one under the sun now.
Now we need to find the ledge and do the one on the tree.
The tree is falling on me!
Whoops.
Uh-oh.
Kill it.
We're fine.
Hopefully I'm not going to anger anyone in here.
Alright, it seems to be good.
Kill it.
Look at this.
Yo, wait, wait, wait, what's this?
What's this?
That's new.
The sound just stopped.
With the... okay, this one is actually going to destroy the musical instrument.
Hold on, I need to be careful here.
Kick it.
I kicked it.
Snowy wasteland?
Dude, the sound is all bugged?
The sound is gone!
Hold on.
I'm actually going to try and restart the game.
I feel like it's very bugged right now.
One sec.
Hopefully that works, because no sound is kind of a bummer.
Let's see.
That's a bug for sure.
Oh wait, it's saying...
Steam cloud error?
Oh no.
What's this?
It says uploading to Steam cloud?
Okay, I'm just going to wait.
Come on.
For some reason it's stuck here on uploading.
I can click the play button, but it says uploading.
Maybe I should wait.
I'm just going to try and open the game.
Synchronizing?
Okay.
Seems good.
All right, I'm back in.
Continue.
I'll be good.
Nice!
Ah, we're back!
Perfect!
Very good.
So there's something in here as well.
Look.
In fact, it's the little...
Oh my god, this is so hard to...
Honestly, I kind of want to remove this one.
Is that crazy?
This is actually a sick...
want.
Dude?
This is actually a sick want.
And there's all of this.
Music for my ears.
I can't do anything yet, though.
I don't know if I should take all this.
Let's just... let's just leave it like this for now.
I hope it's not because look...
totally looks like a musical instrument here, like some kind of...
I hope it doesn't only work with these and you can play some music with it.
Hopefully you can actually put spells in here.
Wait, Manamax 2?
Yikes!
I didn't notice that.
Oh my god.
But...
I mean, I gotta try it.
Let me remove some...
Let me get rid of that.
Get rid of...
Let's get rid of that one.
What else?
I just want to take a couple more of these, basically.
Yeah.
Let's just have a couple of these.
We're gonna play with this later.
It's time to say bye-bye to the black holes and the holy bombs.
They have served us well.
Let's listen to the tree.
Let's keep going.
Oh.
That's right.
There's that thing.
I don't want to take it though.
And in fact, that's not the only one there is.
I found another one of these.
Down below somewhere.
Okay.
Wait.
I see stuff down here.
Wait a minute.
Oh, it's fighting time.
Ooh.
Should I be doing this?
Is this a bad idea?
Oh!
Ancient laboratory.
I'm burning.
It's already a bad idea.
Look at these statues.
What's that?
Teleportation?
What the hell is that thing?
Oh.
I don't like this.
Man, you know what?
I think I should...
I'm tempted to just go down again.
All the way down.
I mean...
Yeah, I'm going to go all the way down again.
We're going down.
I need to heal, man.
If I die, I die.
You know, it is what it is.
Whatever.
Oh no!
Ah, whatever.
I broke it.
God, this spell is so annoying.
It's actually wild.
Why is that even a thing?
Maybe having this on you will unlock something later on when you're somewhere.
It's like a key to a door or something.
What the hell is going on here?
Hello?
What's happening?
What's up, guys?
Where'd you come from?
All right, let's go.
Speed run down to the bottom.
What's that?
Teleportation, huh?
This explosion around me is going to kill me at some point.
For sure.
That is going to be the thing that kills me.
Rain cloud.
No.
That's one.
Oh, hey, nice!
Yo!
Hey, awesome!
What's this?
Return.
No, I don't want that.
Not bad.
Now I kind of regret switching my wand down here.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
No, I cannot edit my wand, unfortunately.
Oh!
Oh, there's a chest!
What was that?
What did I get?
I'm not sure.
I am not sure.
Also, how did I miss that chest?
That was, like, right below the entrance.
Man, I wish I had my teleport wand right now.
Is that going to make this explode?
Thankfully not.
Okay.
Next, next, next, next, next.
Oh, shit, I never...
Let's do this.
Ah, you know what?
No, no, it's easier to do this.
Yeah, nice.
We made it.
Whoa!
I just realized we could have taken a shortcut down here.
But actually, it's good we didn't because the boss is up there and I'm scared of it.
No, sorry, guys, I'm not in the mood to fight.
I'm just in the mood to leave.
Why are there so many enemies?
The fuck's going on?
Did everything respawn?
Yo, what's going on here?
Huh?
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, 100 HP.
Jesus Christ!
We're almost dead.
I don't remember if I have a healing or not.
I just don't remember.
Come on.
Oh, wait, is this going to reflect?
Oh, this is dangerous, isn't it?
I need to... wait, I need to...
Go!
And now we go.
Now we go.
Oh, man, I really hope I have healing.
Don't wait, I have healing!
I restored it!
Oh, my God!
Completely forgot about that, dude.
Fuck, yeah.
Oh, my God.
Holy shit.
Imagine if I died, dude.
Not having remembered that.
Jesus.
Okay.
Let's keep going.
Make a hole here now.
Go, go, go.
Nice.
Jungle time, baby.
Look how much shit I went through.
This is... this is one long run.
There we go.
Super easy.
Super sweet.
Things are getting expensive.
I don't want any of it, though.
I want my teleport wand.
This place.
Ah, shit!
There's enemies!
The hell?
Oh, wait, I'm going... I'm going on a path I haven't gone before.
That's not good.
I need to go a similar path.
I don't know where I went last time, honestly.
Oh, this is insane.
Excuse me!
What the fuck is happening?
Goddamn!
Good thing we have another heal, though.
Alright.
This is the last one, I think.
Shit.
Yeah.
This is the area.
Alright.
Focus up.
We're back.
I see you up there.
Oh, I thought you died.
Doesn't want.
It's been 89 years since I last saw a fresh wand.
Uh-oh.
I hate that guy.
Ah, we don't...
Fuck!
That's annoying.
That's really annoying.
I kind of want to confirm whether or not we take damage.
We have to do this for science.
Yep, I take damage.
I take damage.
Can I get in there some other way?
The fuck?
There's a easy man.
Take it easy, man.
Ah!
What the fuck's going on there?
Stop!
I'm playing careless.
I hate this ghost!
Just fuck you then.
I'm not going that way, I guess.
Uh, cut!
Uh, go here.
Man, where the fuck did I go last time?
Why are there all these enemies?
I feel like I cleansed this area.
Apparently I didn't, unless things respawned.
No, I must have gone a completely different direction.
Let's go here instead.
In fact, I'm just going to heal now.
Oh
yeah, beautiful.
Is there anything inside of here?
I'm slowly going crazy over this constant explosion around me.
I'm going to need to be...
living in the psych ward soon.
This is not good for me.
Slowly driving me nuts.
Bertha?
My screen is shaking a lot.
What the hell is that?
Yo!
A big vat of unstable polymorphine.
That's pretty cool.
I like it.
Come on.
Yeah.
I must be close.
Yeah, I remember this whole area.
There we are.
Okay, it's time.
Oh.
Do not take the health.
Oh, these are sort of cheap.
Bunch of missiles, huh?
Uh, okay.
Yo!
Black holes?
We are back.
But that is black holes with a timer, I believe.
And then what the hell is that?
Let me see if there's some good wants.
So this one has a lot of slots.
Let's see the timers in these.
Cast delay.
A lot of max mana.
0.42.
Yo, this one is very...
What is shuffle?
Fuck shuffle wants.
I kind of like this wand right here.
It seems like a good wand.
But it spells cast too.
I don't like that part.
I kind of want to buy this one to see what this is.
And the wand is decent as well.
Look at the stats on that.
That's really nice.
I'm buying it.
Uh...
That reminds me.
We can try this now.
They can't tell.
But only with two mana...
I wonder if I can work my way around that using add mana.
Or if I need some spell that will actually increase the maximum capacity and not the immediately recharge mana.
Because even though this adds...
How much is it?
30 mana?
Maybe it cannot go above two because this is the max.
You know, it's just going to maximize it to two every time.
So that's like the question that I have.
Let me see this first.
Path of Dark Flame.
Oh, I know what this is!
That's the bullshit the enemy was hitting me with.
That's the thing that did so much damage to me.
Yeah.
Yep.
Quadruple spell.
All right.
But what I really want to try is actually this real quick.
Because I want to see what this does.
Node A.
Literally just plays music.
Node E.
You can make songs with this.
Okay.
Let me try something here.
Let me try.
So this...
So I should not be able to do this.
Oh yeah, it even has a like...
What if I do this?
Oh!
It works!
It actually works!
Okay.
Wait, how does that work with the bar?
So this has...
This is actually okay.
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Point...
I hate the explosion!
I honestly want to kill myself.
I can't deal with this explosion.
It's pissing me off so much.
I can't think.
What an annoying fucking perk.
Oh.
Um...
God damn.
Okay.
Calm down.
Put this there.
This is a fine want.
I can't think.
I can't.
Wait.
Throw this away.
Only four slots.
Let's see here.
Can we do something nice here?
Cast...
Let's try this.
Oh shit.
Oh my God.
That was terrible.
Okay, so it actually just casts a random thing every time.
Oh my God.
Actually good to know that the acid here cuts through this brickwork easily.
Nice to know.
Pretty decent.
Let's try the nuke.
One shot.
One opportunity.
Oh, perks!
I forgot about perks!
No more knockback?
Revenge explosion.
No, I don't want that.
I don't want that.
No, I don't want any of these.
Recharge.
Electricity immunity.
That would be sick.
Glass cannon.
Five times as powerful, but your maximum health becomes 50.
Yeah, no.
That's not happening.
No want tinkering.
Wants cannot be tinkered with, but enemies may drop.
I don't like any of these.
I mean, I like this one.
That's the obvious choice here, obviously.
Right.
Circle of fervor.
Nala.
Let's try the nuke.
Oh, what, what, what, what, what, what, what?
Okay.
Wow.
Interesting.
So that collapses brickwork.
All right.
Got it.
Is there anything I want to try?
I mean, I can't buy anything else.
That's fine.
I don't want any of these anyway.
This is actually a decent one too.
But here's what I want to try real quick.
If I put this here and I just replace all of this, will this technically work?
Because this is infinite mana when I shoot it from the first want.
Is this gonna work?
It actually is.
But look at the board.
It, it shows only, only some of these are being shown.
So that means I don't have enough mana.
I need more ad manas for this to work the way I think it will work.
Mmm, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I wonder if I can make this even better.
Hold on.
If I put this back up here.
And let's say instead of a triple, I use a quadruple.
So that means one, two, three, four.
Is that gonna change anything?
Let me just see here.
Wait, why can't I see the, uh, damage?
Honestly, it's hard to tell the difference here.
I, I can't really tell the difference.
Maybe I like this more.
Who knows?
Nah, whatever.
That's fine.
Uh, so we could actually technically replace this with a double.
But I don't, I don't have a double anymore.
That's fine.
Uh, what do I want to make?
Do I want to make anything?
You know what?
Let's put this here as well.
Because whenever we heal, maybe we want some of this anyway.
That seems good to me.
You know, it's like a buffing wand at this point.
The duration of a projectile is set to zero.
How can I use that?
What is a projectile I would benefit from having no duration?
I'm not so sure.
Oh, dude, I could, I could use a electric charge modifier now that I'm immune to electricity.
I could put that somewhere here.
Is that going to be worth it, though?
Uh, if I remove, wait a minute, what costs a lot of mana here?
Twenty.
This adds thirty.
This is ten mana?
I don't know.
I need, I need one more slot urgently.
Costs eight mana.
Let's just try the, uh...
I'm not sure.
But I kind of want some spell with that on it, you know?
In fact, I don't really have any good spells.
I guess I have these.
Actually, I can use these.
Let's use these.
Let's try something new here.
Uh, put them on...
Oh, wait a minute, I can't really...
Yeah, so I'm not going to use this wand.
I'm going to change it for this.
I'm so sorry, notes.
We're going to play music some other time.
I am pretty dang sure there's some magical combination of music that will open some door or something somewhere.
Like, play the right, uh, notes or whatever and it will happen, you know?
That's what I'm thinking.
That one.
And where's the other one?
There.
So that does a lot of damage.
I can put electricity on that, I guess.
What's this?
Plasma beam bounce?
No, I don't want that.
Let's go through this.
Do we have another modifier?
I think it will shoot out copies of itself when it expires or hits the ground.
I feel like that could be dangerous to myself.
Cast three random spells among the spells in your wand.
Wait, is this going to just save on...
Okay, it casts all of them.
Yeah, okay.
I see.
I thought I could maybe save out on charges doing that.
Probably not.
Oh, actually what I want to do is use a double here.
Or even, I don't have a double, but I have a triple.
So if I do this and I do this, that way it's going to do one, one, two, three.
Let's see.
Yeah, I'm not sure.
Let's just leave it like this.
We're going to do some damage.
In fact, no, no, no, I'm going to...
Do that.
That way.
Now we have lots of... Dude, I kind of want to...
I have explosion immunity.
I also have electricity immunity.
Imagine if I had one of those explosion thunder thingies.
I could go nuts with one of those right now.
That would be sweet.
All right, let's get the fuck out of here.
Oh, before I go, we got to get the...
Oh, hold on.
Remove this.
This is fine.
Rest is good.
Oh, dude.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
No, okay, fine.
Take this.
Now we have healing and we have this.
Then we're going to come back later if we need to heal up.
Beautiful.
Now I have to exit this in the right way as well.
Oh, wait a minute.
Yo, this looks different.
Yo, what?
Oh, hello.
That looks a lot like the boss from the hemisphere.
Are we bossing?
Uh-oh.
The green lion?
Call me Silme!
What the hell?
I'm scared.
All right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right.
We're just doing it.
Oh, shit.
Kill him!
Okay, now he's protected.
Oh, that's lava on both sides.
That's really scary.
Electricity.
Wait, I'm immune.
Oh, shit!
Come on.
Oh, my God, I'm taking damage.
Come on, come on.
Oh, wait, I actually have a lot of HP.
This is going fine.
Oh, almost fell down.
Kill that fucker.
Oh, yeah, I'm draining his shield.
Oh, my God.
I'm actually doing fine.
I'm not losing HP.
He's low HP.
Just stay here, stay here, stay here.
Wait for him to do this other thing.
Call me Silme.
Why do you want me to call you Silme?
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
No more lava?
That's good.
Get it!
Fucking awesome.
Portal to the work?
What?
Do I not get anything?
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Before I move on.
Green, slimy meat.
Can I eat it?
Oh, that makes me sick, huh?
Ingesting slime and more.
Oh, God.
Okay.
Hold on, before we go anywhere.
What's up here?
Yo, there's text!
Can I read that?
I'm glad I'm recording this so I can check this out later.
I feel like, dude, this is not random.
There's definitely a message in there.
And I want to know what it is.
Oh, man.
I'm feeling... I'm feeling like that notebook is gonna come in and play.
Hold on, before I jump in there, I need to see what's down here.
Lava, okay.
That's a bunch of lava.
I'm gonna go back and heal.
Very nice.
1745 health, baby.
That is the most I've ever had, by far.
Also, by the way... Oh, oh, shit, oh, shit!
Don't stand in the lava, you dummy.
We're fine, we're fine.
What was that?
Just there?
I saw something down there.
Oh, maybe not.
Huh?
I thought I saw a spider!
Probably wrong, then.
Okay.
Portal to the work.
Enter the work!
Golden statue.
Wait, what?
Pick the golden sta- You got 40,000 gold?
Okay!
There's a hand.
Oh my god, I wish I could read this.
Complete the work?
What?
Wait a minute.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, what?
Complete what work?
What's over here?
I kind of wish I had the all seeing eye right now.
Did I make my way through?
Wait a minute.
Oh no,
definitely not.
Wait a minute.
Oh, that's that's a heavy wall.
Okay, complete the work.
What?
Death Midas.
Credits.
Credits, baby!
Okay!
My first run!
I freaking did it!
What is all this?
Wait Midas, as in gold?
Hand of Midas?
Dude, man.
But I'm not done!
I have many things to do.
Let's see if I can pronounce some of these names.
Jokulabonan.
Yukkyu Kaleo.
Man, I fucking did it.
I won.
I'm a winner.
With the only wand.
That I've made that is actually amazing.
Wait, Nala games?
Oh, the spell is called Nala.
That's interesting, isn't it?
Completed the game.
You are dead.
Click here for stats.
Only took 45 deaths.
Look at all these records.
I guess time is not... I guess the lower the time, the better, right?
This would not count as a record, the higher.
Dude, this was awesome.
Damn.
Total wins won.
Streaks won.
Hell yeah.
Orbs collected four.
Okay.
Oh, I clicked too late, I guess.
There's nothing there now.
Progress.
Man, I discovered a ton of stuff.
What's this?
Kalmamatu.
I don't know what that is actually.
Look how many spells I haven't even found yet.
How is that real?
Look how many perks I haven't seen yet.
Oh, all the yellow ones are the ones that I discovered in this run?
I guess.
Because I discovered Holy... No, wait.
I used Holy Bomb in this run.
Nuke, take cover.
I found that.
How there's so many enemies I haven't seen.
I guess... Okay, that's not surprising.
There are still many areas I haven't explored yet.
But I intend to.
Hamunvaitaya.
Wait, what?
Matkijia?
Wait.
Is there...
Is there a mimic in this game that I have killed without knowing it?
Are there actually mimics?
I did not pay attention.
I'm thinking Dark Souls type mimic here for those that are initiated to that sort of thing.
Man, look how many spells there are!
How did I not... I found like half!
And there's still all these perks.
It's crazy that there's still all these perks left, but I feel like I'm getting a lot of the same perks.
Every time, you know what I mean?
Okay.
Six secrets found.
Wait, discovered the secret below.
The secret below?
It's gotta be the work.
What else could count as a secret here?
Oh, you know what?
Probably the research notes could be a secret.
Oh my God, look at this.
165 out of 422.
I forgot there was a percentage up here.
Only 40% of spells discovered.
Damn!
I mean, I discovered most enemies.
Not most, but like more than half, let's say.
Fuck yeah, man.
Okay.
We go again.
There's things I want to do.
Unfortunately, not right now.
Because I have other things to do on this Friday.
But that was awesome, man!
I fucking did it!
I'm gonna keep playing this game because I want to discover more secrets.
I want to find more spells.
I want to find more perks.
I want to kill everyone!
And make awesome ones.
I fucking did it, dude.
Save and quit.
Hells yeah.
Hold on.
Hey, everyone's cheering with the hymns.
Congrats on completing the tutorial.
Thank you, Mr. Beat.
Thank you.
I feel... You know how the tablet says...
Calls me uninitiated?
I feel like I'm a little initiated now.
Just a tiny amount.
Tutorial complete.
Oliver wins.
Yes!
Freaking awesome.
God damn.
Man!
A reef!
And a laevie!
Giving out five community subs each.
Thank you so much, reef.
Also a laevie.
It's good to see you again.
Thank you for that.
You guys are amazing.
I have over 200 subscribers now on Twitch.
Thanks to all of you.
How's everyone doing, huh?
Yeah, win with just 45 deaths is very good.
I don't know if you're being sarcastic or not, but I'll take that.
I feel like I'm good at this game.
I feel like I'm actually decent.
There's still things I don't quite understand and it's a little...
I'm still janking a little bit around with the wands.
You know?
But...
Man, is it fun.
Don't worry about cloud saving stuff, by the way.
That's normal.
Sometimes your save file gets so large that the game and Steam struggle to deal with it on the cloud.
Oh, okay.
Well, I guess I always have a local copy of it, right?
The thing I'm usually afraid of is if there's an older version that gets overwritten.
You know, if you have a local copy and a cloud copy.
Maybe my save didn't get uploaded or whatever and then it downloads the one from the cloud and overwrites my old.
I don't know.
Or my new ones with the old, that's like a fear I have.
Not sarcastic at all.
It's pretty good.
Thank you so much.
I love saying your name.
It was a great experience.
You were quite good and played blind as well.
I see people with 200 plus play time on Reddit who did not finish the game.
So you are good.
I really tried to though.
Like I try hearted a lot.
I played slowly and meticulously, mostly.
So I really, really did my best, you know.
I would recommend disabling cloud.
It regularly breaks saves.
Oh, okay.
You know what?
I will follow that advice actually.
I can totally do that.
See, even now it has trouble uploading.
It's just stuck on uploading when I look at Steam.
That's problematic.
I have disabled cloud.
There it is.
If you ever want to back up, just be sure it's in local low in the save folder.
Okay.
I'm just going to Google how to back up.
I will figure out a way to do it.
Oh, that's right, JJ.
Steam actually does ask.
That's true.
I have that happen before.
I forgot about that.
But you know, sometimes I'm unsure.
It asks me, hey, do you want to keep the local one or the cloud one?
And I'm like, I don't know, which is the newer one.
So that's when I get a little paranoid.
The game actually suggests to disable cloud saves once they reach certain size.
Really?
That's interesting.
Oh, if you reinstall your PC, remember to save the Noida save folder.
That's a good point.
I do nuke my PC once a year or so.
DunkerSlam had his run save get bricked due to cloud save.
He had to restore to an older save from a week ago.
I don't know who DunkerSlam is, but I guess it's some kind of streamer.
What's it like being a true wizard?
Dude, it feels amazing.
It feels incredible.
I feel like I have mastered the elements.
But it also feels like I've just scratched the surface of this game.
Haha, yet I wizard Oliver.
I love that meme.
Dunk is one of the Noida gods on Twitch.
Oh, okay.
Is he really good at the game?
He's a Noida prophet?
I love that.
Oliver, you can now cast Fireball in real life.
Fuck yeah, dude!
That's all I've ever wanted.
I always play wizards in video games, actually.
When I played World of Warcraft, Mage, all the time.
I would cast Frostbolts mostly, though.
Not Fireball, but still.
In fact, whenever I can, I usually choose Wizard, if there's an option.
Or like, anything magic.
I love magic.
Haha, new Noida Messiah.
If you ever get to the point of looking things up about Noida, watch some DunkerSlam.
Oh, I just understood the name.
Dunk or Slam.
I read it as DunkerSlam.
I understand.
I think this game has like, one or two areas?
What do you mean?
Every time I see Noida, I feel the urge to go for another run and make some cool ones.
You know, you should.
Whenever you see Noida, just go out and go for a run.
It's really healthy.
Real life has friendly fire.
Spell Summon Coke.
Man.
Wouldn't that be something?
Are you a mage in Souls games?
Uh, sometimes.
Depends.
I like to do a mix of both.
I like to, if I can, to do the Gandalf style, you know?
Sword and magic.
That's the best.
And you know what the best, or like, my main reason for that is?
I feel like I'm missing out on so much in Souls games, if I don't use the magic.
Because there's so much of it, usually.
And I feel like whenever I just run around with a sword, I mean, I'm pretty good with a sword, but...
I feel like there's just so much I'm missing.
Battle Mage?
Exactly.
That's it.
Yeah.
I'm basically greedy, okay?
I wanna try it all at once.
It's probably not very optimal.
You know?
Having a bit of everything.
If you saw my, uh...
Okay, actually I'm not gonna spoil Bloodborne, if you haven't seen that, but...
I'm doing a little bit of that, as much as I can, at least.
I'm not very efficient with my build, but I like to do as much as I can at once, you know?
Hey JJ!
Welcome.
Thanks for subscribing.
What is your final thoughts on Subnautica Below Zero?
I thought it was a great game.
I think I liked the first one more, though.
It was just a little cooler atmosphere, you know?
Throughout that game.
Although, it was also my first time in Subnautica, so that also, of course, does something to you.
There are certain things I like more in the first, and certain things I like more in the second.
But they're both excellent games.
I would say the story is better in the first.
I also didn't like that they voiced the main character in the second.
I mean, it was fine, you know, but I would probably prefer if they didn't.
How about Cruelty Squad?
I don't know what that is.
Oh, it's a random game.
I haven't heard about Cruelty Squad.
Let me Google that.
Cruelty Squad.
Sounds like some kind of Marvel thing.
Tactical First Person Shooter.
With tactical stealth elements.
Oh my god.
These screenshots give me...
makes me think I'm high on mushrooms.
I have not heard about that, but holy shit, it has a lot of positive reviews on Steam.
So I think it's a good game, I guess.
Mike from DS.
Well, I think we'd both agree the second was significantly cooler.
Nice.
Good one.
I mean, in some aspects it was.
I liked the music better in the second.
But the first one had excellent music too, you know?
It's just like a tiny amount better.
It was just perfect.
SCP Containment Breach is a game I recommend.
A bit of an older one, but good.
I know what SCP is, I think.
Isn't that...
That's like an imaginary universe type deal, isn't it?
I guess it's a horror game.
SCP Containment Breach.
Remastered?
Is that the one?
I see the one on Steam here.
Probably the one.
Have you played Myst Riven?
Riven just got a remake recently.
I have not, New Cherdsky.
Actually, my real life friend gave me a heads up about that.
Maybe I should check it out.
In fact, I'm going to put that on my backlog.
Because I actually do want to try those games.
Riven.
2024.
There we go.
So, in case you want to know what I've played or not played, you can check this out.
It shows all the games that are on my backlog.
SCP is a writing platform focusing on a secretive foundation that contains anomalous things.
Yes, exactly.
That's what I've heard.
I think I read a couple of entries at some point in the past.
It was very, actually very creepy.
You know?
Yeah, it's a creepy pasta is a rumor that a foundation called the SCP Foundation.
Which above all, government is containing very dangerous entities.
Yeah.
Yep.
Okay, I know exactly what that is now.
I think it's also stood for something.
Secure containment protocol or something, right?
It's not like direct horror, but it's just like...
It's a weird kind of horror that is very scary.
Because your brain fills out the rest.
And it's just very, very, like, odd.
And the oddness of it all is the scariest part, you know?
Okay, I gotta get to the store and grab some food.
I'm gonna raid someone on Twitch here.
Let's see who's streaming Noita.
And send you guys over to that.
You can say hi there.
Rest of raid there.
Raid channel.
Same category.
Let's see who's streaming.
There's a guy called Ochiniva.
I wonder if there's someone playing this blind for the first time.
Okay, there's a guy here who just made affiliate on Twitch with 13 viewers.
I'm gonna send you over to him.
It's gonna be nice.
So thank you everybody for watching, for subscribing and just having a blast here and hanging out and chatting.
It's so cool to see you all.
And I hope you're having a wonderful Friday.
I'm gonna click this button now and you'll be send off.
Have a good night everybody.
I'll see you in the next stream.
Bye-bye.